You're telling me to hide a
mirror inside the wedding cake?
Uh-huh.
Is that a cool way to
make an entrance or what?
It'll be like bam, and I come
flying out of that huge cake.
It's gonna be so funny.
Trust me on this one.
I told you I don't need to be funny.
Now listen to me, kid.
You got one job.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
You want me to break the picture, right?
But I can do that and
have a cool entrance.
You'll be as good as dead.
You think it's wise to
destroy Mama's wedding cake?
Do you know how much
she's been looking forward
to it and how angry she'll
be when that happens?
You made copies of my friends
back in the woods, right?
Uh-huh.
First, she captures someone's
reflection in a mirror.
Then she projects it onto an
animal and transforms them.
Yeah, I can do that, so what?
I captured all of these, so
could you turn them into me?
Father?
Vito, all wrapped up?
Everything is ready to go, Lili.
All right, nice work.
I guess it's on now.
This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope that we'll never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm so truly grateful I ran into
you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment with tears in
our eyes till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you wanna fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
And no matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting times
we'll reach and we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then, but as
for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice that
can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated, it
crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I
swear, I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer,
together I'm telling you.
In our path I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea, I'm torn
it, cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that I wanna take you to.
Let's head forward then,
but ask for the way.
We already know.
We promised it long ago.
Who are these people?
And why were they in the cake?
what a scoop brilliant frankly I've
become desensitized to
the spectacle oh Oh, no,
this is big news.
Look closer.
That's a pirate from the worst generation.
Straw Hat Luffy.
The unimaginable is happening right now.
He's starting a fight with Big Mom.
Oh, there are so many Straw Hats.
They can't all be him.
Run away.
The cake is collapsing.
What do they even want?
Straw Hat, Luffy, again?
You're gonna pay for this.
You're gonna be all right.
No turning back now.
This is the big moment. There!
What's going on, Mat-dor?
I thought that Straw
Hat Luffy and that other
Gourmet of his died in the prison library.
Damn it.
Opera, you dunce.
I knew you were lying.
Just trying to save your
own useless hide, huh?
My cake!
My precious cake!
Look at it!
It's ruined!
Uh-oh.
She's acting weird.
I was looking forward to it, too.
I understand.
I'm upset, too, but you
have to keep your composure.
Oh, my cake.
Head chef, you have
got to get out of here.
Mama's going to freak out.
I want a cake and you're
going to bring me a new one.
But that's impossible. Oh!
Life...
or...
wedding cake!
Oh no!
It's the soul Pucci!
What a scoop!
She's snatching up their life force!
Anyone who fears death even a little
is vulnerable to this technique!
And who isn't afraid of dying, right?
Ah! Look! There it is!
Please don't steal my life away, Father!
This is the price you
pay for ruining my fun!
Your life is now mine
to do with as I please!
Okay, let's go.
You enjoyed that cake.
I heard a loud yell.
Big Mom's really freaking
out—is this part of their plan?
Our plan's gone off the
rails too hard to say.
If this chaos will help or
not, I swear you're gonna pay!
pay
Pedro, have you sent them all?
This Luffy is the last one.
It's time to cause some chaos
ourselves, friend. Good.
I've been waiting.
I'm sure Sanji could use some backup.
You guys ready?
Got your earplugs? Uh-huh.
I'm totally screen-proof.
And we're supposed to
rescue Sanji's family.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, we'll leave the rest to you.
Don't screw this up, loser.
Is he really that bad?
Yeah, he's the worst.
Once I get my heart back,
I'll teach them a lesson.
I have had all I can stand of you.
Wretched little pest!
Get back here!
Straw Hat, which one is you?
Well then, monkey dear Yuffie, now
that I know who you are, come here.
Let's have a chat in the new world.
You're making stupid excuses, big mom.
You haven't become king of
the pirates and that's on you.
Get over here and fight me!
I'm not backing down even
if you are an emperor.
I'm taking sonja back no matter what.
I'm gonna turn this all
around and make you sorry!
The perfect cake.
It just collapsed.
You bastard!
It's not fair!
How dare you ruin the wedding cake!
Which one of you is real? Show yourself!
Where are you, Squat?
What, are you stupid?
Why would he do that?
I'll murder you.
Get over here!
This is obviously a diversion.
He's not going to respond to you, moron.
I'm right over here!
He...
He responded!
If you wanna fight, then you got one!
I'll tear you limb from limb!
That's it.
There's the photo.
Kaido, Vito, got that
launcher ready, I hope.
Uh-huh.
Ready to go, Lili, at any time. Father.
All right, Straw Hat, don't screw this up.
Let me go, you awful beast!
They're coming in hordes!
I'm waiting!
That one must be the real Luffy, huh?
Lay low till he breaks the picture.
Then we wait three seconds and move.
Hey, this is serious.
Are you even listening?
What are you hearing?
Come on, Zeus!
Here, Mama.
Prometheus!
Ready to shine!
We're gonna take out the
whole crowd in one shot!
Got it!
Too easy!
Now suck on this!
Almost there.
Come, come!
What the?
This is the real one.
The other Straw Hats are animals that
were transformed by Brulé's ability.
He must have gathered them
in the seducing woods.
Don't pay them any mind. I see.
In that case, they must
have captured Barrel.
Dammit!
Is this somebody's power?
My arms and legs are stuck in here!
What is this weird thing?
Katakuri, are you trying to save me?
I know you're my son,
but I can handle this.
That's not it, mama; he's not after you!
He's after mother, Carmel's portrait!
But how do you know the
importance of that portrait?
Only people close to the family
should have that information.
Spit it out. Who told you? Who cares?
Let me out, dammit!
Well, ain't this a fine mess.
Somebody, anybody, break
that picture, quick!
Lupe!
Dammit!
Leave it to me, Pedro!
Help me!
Full shot current!
Shoulder throw!
Go away!
Going to explain my powers now, are you?
Oh, man!
Katakuri wields the power of the Mochi
Mochi fruit, a parametheotide like yours.
Jinbei!
You can get away from its hold with
liquid, but better to stay away.
What's this now?
Just to be clear, I'm the one who
told Luffy about Mother Carmel.
As your ally, I heard
rumors of certain incidents.
Bunch of miscreants!
Did they come to take back Sanji?
They really think they can
escape here with their lives?
And the wedding's ruined at any rate.
Well, I'll be damned.
I thought Straw Hat was dead.
Don't worry, members
of the Vinsmoke family.
The Charlotte siblings shall take care
of this little matter lickety-split.
Lick.
What's this about?
I thought you said you wouldn't
be leaving our alliance,
and yet you defended the little
interlover who ruined my cake!
To be clear, am I to interpret
this as an outright mutiny? Well?
That is a fair assessment
of the situation.
Ha!
You've got some nerve.
As of now, I am departing your crew.
...because it is my intention
to join the Straw Hats!
That's what I call big news!
The former warlord Jinbei wants
to join the Straw Hat Pirates!
Well, fine then.
After you leave, you can do as you choose.
But if you recall our previous talk,
you still need to pay the
price before I let you go.
Otherwise, you would be betraying the
generosity I showed you. Of course.
So long as you promise me that no harm
will come to the rest of the Sun Pirates.
As for my own lifespan, I'll gladly
offer up as much as you can take.
Jinbei!
Your plan doesn't make sense!
How can you join my crew if you die?
I get my treat after all.
But it's such a shame.
You really hate me that much.
You want to leave this paradise
I've worked so hard to build.
Even if it kills you.
Well, you won't get my pity.
She's gonna use the soul focus again.
Let's go.
You know how the deal works?
So what will it be?
Stay!
Or life!
Make your choice!
I choose life!
It's over.
Yep, he's done for now.
The death of Jimei!
What a scoop!
It's time to die!
I said stay or life!
His soul won't budge.
It doesn't work.
I can't believe it.
That means he's not afraid
of Mama's power even a bit.
Did you think I would falter?
The man who I have chosen to follow will
surely be king of the pirates someday.
I can't be intimidated by
a mere emperor of the sea.
She can't do it.
She can't take away Jinbei's lifespan.
If I can't pay you in spirit,
then I shall return this sake cup.
My pledge renounced?
I now officially depart
from the Big Mom Pirates.
I thank you for the generosity
that you've shown me.
All this chaos.
And he just cuts right through it.
I can't believe how awesome he is!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha! Yeah!
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ma ma ma ma!
Congratulations, Jinbei!
You've made a powerful enemy.
I hope you're happy.
Chop!
That's the portrait of Mother Carmel.
He just destroyed it.
Oh, my word.
Now that is some big news.
Mama.
Way to go!
He did it!
Nice work!
What the heck?
So one of those fake Straw Hats
wasn't an animal after all?
All right, good.
Big Mom saw the busted portrait.
Just a few seconds before
she blows her wig. Oh!
He's acting odd. What the devil?
We have the deadly poison
K-X Launcher's ready to fire.
He ripped the skin off his own face?
Come on!
This is my face!
He's so freaky!
So, King, is that you?
You're alive.
I thought you died.
Well I did.
But it was years ago.
What have you done?
Do you know who that is?
Oh.
My picture.
Oh poor mother.
What's going on isn't
she supposed to yell!
Stay away!
This has happened before!
Mama's gonna go crazy!
Do you have any idea
what you've done here?
And you monsters have destroyed
my lovely wedding cake too?
I see what's happening here.
Mama's in shock.
She's gonna go mad—let's kill
Straw Hat before it gets ugly!
Luffy:
We must stand firm until Big Mom
begins to scream and panic. Okay?
You're gonna die!
die Oh, boy!
Leave me alone!
Hey!
It definitely hurts!
Are you okay, Pudding?
Let's find someplace safe.
Pudding, stop!
Be quiet!
Look!
This is the real me!
See? You surprised?
Or maybe disappointed.
Not to worry, though.
You won't have to live with the truth!
I've been conning idiots
like you my entire life.
You're so easy to deceive.
And what about you?
What?
What I mean is, you've also been
deceiving yourself, Pudding, haven't you?
Shut up!
What would you know?
Don't have to play. You understand?
Drop it, Pudding. Back off!
Pudding.
Please tell me you're okay.
You screwed this one up.
You useless twit!
We don't have time to
screw around like this.
Things can't proceed to this chunk dies.
Let me go!
GD, come on out!
GD!
Who the hell is this guy?
It's Dyefunko, no!
Wait a sec, I promise that
I can finish the job, okay?
You already had your chance
and completely blew it.
Now take a seat.
Hang on, Pudding!
It's over, Collier Spray!
Enough already!
Don't use my power anymore!
Please I beg you my heart
is on the line. I'll have no
You guys don't give up, huh?
What's your Put a sock in
it and head of security,
remember they'll catch on if I sit back.
I've captured a captain—great kill! him?
him
You know, that ain't a bad idea.
Stop messing around!
Just shut up. Listen.
We hit a snag.
What's keeping Big Mom from screaming?
I can't stall much longer!
Stop, Jinbei! Oven?
Now you'll pay!
Be careful, Pedro.
Don't let him make contact.
With you, what the hell?
I think I
remember you,
Pedro.
You were Peckham's brother
in arms, weren't you?
If I recall correctly, you lost your
eye and a chunk of your life when you.
You miserably failed to
steal Mama's poli-glyph.
By daring to show your face here again,
I can only assume you're ready to die.
Don't be a fool.
I've always been ready.
I'm gonna cook you alive.
It's been three seconds.
How long do we wait?
What is the hold-up?
Isn't Big Mom supposed
to be yelling right now?
You okay?
I'm alive.
Well, I mean, Dad.
How are you doing?
Didn't know you could pop your head off.
Luffy: We need to get back to the matter
at hand, what the blazes is going on?
How dare you try
something like this on us!
Hurry veggie, get off of me!
Damn it—this wasn't supposed to happen.
happen What is the
meaning of this big mob?
I trusted you!
You're licked.
What about our agreement?
Even in the underworld, we are a decency.
Answer me!
A little late to whine
about it now, Father.
We sure walked into this one, huh?
This candy has us bound.
They swiped all our weapons at the gate.
They even have our raid suits.
Looks like we fell for the perfect setup.
I guess we aimed too high, huh?
What is wrong with you? Stop laughing!
I hate to say it, but you're the
one who made your sons this way.
Father.
They don't even fear their own death.
They may be my brothers, but I
can hardly even see them as human.
Oh, my goodness.
As far as assassinations
go, this is quite sad.
I feel like I'm just squashing a bug.
Utter cruelty.
Are you tongue-tied, judge?
You're making jokes?
I've worked so hard.
I've devoted my life to this.
All for the sake of vengeance against
the countries of the North Blue.
I've shed blood, sweat, and
tears for the Jeremiah Empire.
Big Mom!
What do you have to say for yourself?
Answer me!
What a miserable sight you are.
What's this?
Jerma's gonna get wiped out.
Oh-ho, the news just doesn't stop today.
Jerma's leader's bawling his eyes out.
Please tell me.
This is all a lie!
Don't even bother.
Mama's in a state of shock.
You're wasting your breath
trying to get through to her.
I admit when Mother Carmel's portrait
shattered, I felt a knot in my stomach.
But it seems that Mama's anger
pushed her over the edge,
so in a sense we're in lickety luck.
I do understand your burning ambition
and delusions of grandeur, Judge.
Lickety.
But think of it this way.
Would you listen to a cattle's plea when
you've been looking forward to a steak?
Once we consume, you will be unstoppable.
All thanks to Germa.
We need to go help them out!
Luffy, wait. Listen to me.
Tread carefully.
Big Mom is having an emotional overload
and doesn't know what to focus on first.
I think we should show her
the broken picture again.
Sure, if you say so, that's
what we'll do, buddy!
That ship is sailed.
Yeah, something wrong?
That tall guy from before is coming.
Katakuri.
Okay, change your heart.
I'm thinking that approach will work
Katakuri's looking pale as a ghost.
You see that?
It means he saw a future
where the things get messy.
Do your thing, Straw Hat.
Just leave it to me!
Jinbei! Pedro! Come on!
We gotta back Straw
Hat up with all we got.
Follow me!
Hey, Allied Forces!
The time has come!
Equip your Invisible Symphonia!
Invisible Symphonia?
The Airflags!
Buggy?
What's he shouting about? Hello?
Can you pull it off?
It's our last shot!
And the only way we can take
everyone out simultaneously!
Buggy.
What's taking so long?
Shoot Straw Hat
I'm good, Paulie.
Got it! Right!
So all I gotta do is show Big Mom this
thing Everything will be back on track,
right?
Flambeau shot go!
You can only peep slightly ahead, huh?
Now, ain't that a pity?
But that ain't some special
privilege, you know.
Even if we can't see it ourselves,
we all have an equal right
to change the future.
Hehehehe.
Ah, strut.
Ha, ha, ha.